[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Різноманітний' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いろんな"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Подорож' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たび"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Листочок' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はっぱ"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Ікебана (мистецтво квітів)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いけばな"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Смажений батат' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "やきいも"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Справи' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ようじ"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Д,З' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しゅくだい"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Жахіття' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たいへん"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Автобусна зупинка' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "バスてい"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Охоронець, вахта' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "もんばん"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Стояти у ряд' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ならびます"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Національний' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "こくりつ"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'Наприклад' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たとえば"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the word 'Урок' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "じゅぎょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the word 'Простий' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かんたん"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the word 'Солодощі' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おかし"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the word 'Здивування' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "びっくり"
    }
]